欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
我叫伊莱沙·斯嘉丽
My name is Eliza Scarlet.
是个私家侦探
I'm a private detective.
还有 拜托千万别说 你是个啥
And, please, don't say, "You're a what? "
我现在负责伦敦办事处了
ELIZA: I'm running this London office now,
我敢保证 情况会有所好转的
and I can assure you, things will pick up.
我们基本上一个客户都没有
We have exactly no clients.
极端时刻需要极端手段
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
不要四处又嗅又刨的
WILLIAM: No sniffing around or digging.
我又不是狗 威廉
I'm not a dog, William.
你做了什么啊
What have you done? !
-你看上很累  -你看上去很美
You look tired. You look beautiful.
在纳什父子
Here at Nash and Sons,
我们提供最专业的服务
we offer the most professional of services.
我不是吹嘘哈 过去几个月在我的领导下
And I do not boast when I say that these past few months
我们取得了很大的成功
under my leadership have seen even greater success.
一位女性 掌管着
A woman, no less, at the helm
伦敦最受尊敬的私家侦探机构
of London's most esteemed private detective agency.
伊莱沙·斯嘉丽 首席调查员
Eliza Scarlet, chief investigator.
戈弗雷先生 斯嘉丽里面是一个T
One T in Scarlet, Mr Godfrey.
正如你所见 我的成功不言而喻
As you can see, my success here speaks for itself.
抱歉打扰一下
CLARENCE: Sorry to disturb you,
斯嘉丽小姐 但我需要你
Miss Scarlet, but I need your sign- off
在惠特洛克案件调查上签字
on the Whitlock case investigation.
当然
Of course.
这是我们众多成功案例中的一个
Another successful conclusion to one of our many cases.
请能确保我们的地址
And if you could ensure that our address is placed
在文章的显著部位出现 戈弗雷先生
somewhere prominent in the article, Mr. Godfrey.
多少次了
How many times?
是惠特洛克案件或者惠特洛克调查
It's the Whitlock case or the Whitlock investigation,
不要案件和调查两个词一起用
not both.
纳什先生雇我
I was not hired by Mr. Nash
又不是假扮私家侦探的
to pretend to be a private detective.
三次了
So you said, three times.
谢谢各位
Thank you, everyone.
你们现在都知道流程了
You know the drill by now.
-斯嘉丽小姐 我能说句心里话吗  -不能
Miss Scarlet, may I speak my mind? No.
我知道纳什先生的全体员工
I know it's not ideal that Mr. Nash's entire
-都离开了你的确很糟糕  -谢谢
staff of men have left you. Thank you
用遗弃来形容更合适
Deserted is more an appropriate term.
但当他在巴黎时
But whilst he's in Paris,
确保他的生意不亏本
it is my number- one responsibility
是我的首要责任
to make sure his business is financially viable.
也是我的 谢谢
As it is mine- thank you.
所以 所以 作为他的会计
So, so, as his accountant, I must advise you
我强烈建议你
in the strongest possible terms
你这么花钱是非常不谨慎的
that this, this financial practice is not prudent.
谢谢 谢谢 斯嘉丽小姐
Thank you. Thank you, Miss Scarlet
我知道自己在做什么 克拉伦斯
I know what I'm doing, Clarence.
真的吗
Really?
真的吗 因为 因为请演员
Really? Because, because hiring actors
来假扮调查员是非常不理智的
to pretend to be detectives tells me otherwise!
我算了算
So, I've done some sums.
我们的财务状况
And our financial situation
不像我们当初想的那么糟
is not as bad as we first thought.
而是更糟糕了
It is worse.
因此我对雇佣
Hence my reservations
演员假扮雇员持保留意见
at hiring actors who purport to be employees.
-这就是浪费钱  -不是
It's a waste of money. It's not.
《警察新闻画报》将发表一篇文章
The Illustrated Police News" will publish an article
宣称自纳什先生让我负责以来
declaring our success
我们取得了成功的业绩
since Mr. Nash left me in charge.
这会为我们吸引更多的客户
This, in turn, will attract more clients.
更多的意思是原本就很多
The term"more" implies we already have a full roster.
可是我上次查看时发现
But the last time I checked, we have exactly
我们一个客户都没有
no clients.
我不想把责任
I do not wish to lay blame
完全归咎于你
squarely at your door.
很好 因为他们不想让女人
Good, because the fact they didn't want a woman
管账是生物学问题 而不是过错
running their accounts is a question of biology, not fault.
纳什先生的手下们也是一样
And the same goes for Mr. Nash's staff of men.
我记得纳什先生的手下离开
My recollection is that Mr. Nash's men left
是因为你对待他们的方式
because of the manner in which you dealt with them.
他们中的一半人吃完午饭后就不回来了
Half of them never returned after their lunch
另一半人则想什么时候上班就什么时候上班
and the other half strolled into work when it suited.
我的管理更为严格
I was trying to run a tighter ship.
纳什先生的方式
: Well, Mr. Nash's way
则更为尊重
was a little more respectful.
克拉伦斯 需要我再提醒你一遍他已经不在这了吗
Clarence, need I remind you that he's not here anymore?
我现在负责伦敦办事处了
I'm running this London office now,
我敢保证 情况会有所好转的
and I can assure you, things will pick up.
既然你这么说
If you say so.
我就是这么说的
I do.
给我从费尔顿街到布里奇巷的当地人才档案
WILLIAM: Get me the files on the local talent from Felton Street
任何会用刀的都要
to Bridge Lane, anyone handy with a knife.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你去调查一下死者的亲戚
You track down the dead man's relatives,
-通知他们死者被刺的事  -马上去 长官
inform them of the stabbing. Straightaway, sir.
-嘿 公爵  -现在没空
Hey, Duke...Not now.
长官
OFFICER: Sir!
现在不行
: Not now!
好了 我们开始吧
AII right, let's get started.
我说了 安静点
I said, quiet!
现在 我知道上个月很难熬
Now, I know this last month has been difficult
简直地狱一般
Diabolical, more like.
但刚刚证实
But it has just been confirmed that,
除了新加的埃塞克斯郡和肯特郡以外
as well as the additional areas in Essex and Kent,
我们现在还将负责
we'll now be policing further districts
萨里和米德尔塞克斯郡的治安管理
in Surrey and Middlesex, too.
该死 头儿
Bloody hell, skipper,
我们已经捉襟见肘了
we're flat- out as it is.
为了满足需求 所有假期都将取消
To cope with demand, all leave will be canceled
同时实行两班倒
and double shifts implemented.
我说现在没空了
I said not now!
-是急事 长官  -什么东西
It's urgent, sir. What's this?
赶紧开工吧
Get to it, then.
菲茨罗伊 菲尔普斯
Fitzroy, Phelps.
如果我需要你的意见 查理 我会问你的
Listen, if I want your opinion, Charlie, I will ask for it.
我自己没有做的事
I'm not telling you to do anything
我也不会让你做
that I'm not already doing myself.
我都已经几天没回家了
I haven't been home for days.
我知道 头儿 抱歉
I know, skipper- - sorry.
好吧 梅菲尔地区发生了枪击案
Right, there's been a shooting in Mayfair.
听上去像是持械抢劫
Sounds like an armed robbery.
是特纳街尽头的那个地方
It's that place at the end of Turner Street.
极乐境
The Temple of Elysium.
是个剧院吗
Is it a theater?
不是 孩子
No, son.
不是剧院
It ain't no theater.
你好啊帅哥
Hello, handsome.
之前来过警察 我已经给过口供了
I've already given my statement to the officer
我的姑娘们也一样
that was here earlier, as did my girls.
你们需要放她们回家
I really must insist that they be allowed home.
她们都工作一晚上了
They've been working all night.
虽然如此 但我还是需要你和她们
Well, that is as may be, but I need you and them
给我讲述一下事情经过
to tell me the chain of events.
所以是一个持械歹徒闯进了妓院
So, an armed gunman entered the brothel
这里不是妓院
It's not a brothel.
这是个精英绅士俱乐部
It is an elite gentlemen's club.
一个持械歹徒闯进了精英绅士俱乐部
An armed gunman entered the elite gentlemen's club,
打劫后开枪射中了其中一个嫖客
robbed it, then shot one of your punters.
一个持械歹徒从前门进来
A gunman came through the entrance.
他用枪指着我们的门卫
He held our watchman
要求他把自己绑起来
at gunpoint and demanded that he tie himself up.
然后他从一间卧室到另一间卧室打劫我的客户
Then he went from bedroom to bedroom robbing my clients.
我的门卫想办法给自己松了绑
My watchman managed to untie himself.
然后他出去呼救
And then he went outside calling for help,
而不是对付歹徒 保护我的姑娘们
instead of tackling the gunman and protecting me and my girls,
我花钱雇他就是干这个的
which is what he's paid to do.
你需要去局里
You'll need to come to the station
做个笔录 先生
to make a statement, sir.
能给我描述一下枪手的长相吗
PHELPS: I need a description of the gunman.
他用黑围巾蒙住了脸
A black scarf covering his face,
破旧的布帽和大衣
shabby cloth cap and overcoat,
中等身高 金发蓝眼睛
average height, fair hair, and blue eyes.
我们还需要跟
PHELPS: We'll need to talk
你的嫖客们谈谈
to your punters, too.
他们都离开了
Well, they've all left.
这是个私人俱乐部 警探
This is a private club, Detective.
先生们来到极乐境
Gentlemen come to the Temple of Elysium
是为了与我的某位女神共度私密时光的
to enjoy some discreet time with one of my goddesses.
而不是为了
Not to be part of
参与警方的调查
some police investigation.
关于这一点 你知道希腊女神实际上住在奥林匹斯山
On that, were you aware that Greek goddesses
而不是极乐世界吗
actually lived on Mount Olympus, not Elysium?
极乐世界
Elysium was a paradise
是给众神青睐的勇士们住的
for warriors favored by the gods.
我是说 可能会有些女勇士
I mean, there may have been some women there...
是的 谢谢你的讲授 菲茨罗伊警探
Yes, thank you for the lesson, Detective Fitzroy.
非常吸引人
Fascinating, I'm sure.
那被枪射中的嫖客呢
What about the punter who was shot?
他们不是嫖客
: They are not punters!
他们是绅士访客
They are gentleman callers.
那么这个绅士访客
PHELPS: So, this gentleman caller
因为过度放纵而睡着了
was sleeping off some overindulgence
当闯入者试图打劫时
and the intruder tried to rob him,
他们打了起来
and a fight ensued.
我想就是因为这个他才中枪吧
Which I assume is why the fella got shot.
那么
So.
谁给他处理的伤势
: Who tended to him?
我们一个姑娘正好是个医生
One of my girls happened to be with a doctor.
她给他检查了伤势然后送他去医院了
He examined him and took him off to hospital.
那这个医生对他的伤势是怎么说的
And what did this doctor say about his injuries?
我没问
I never asked.
那他去了那家医院呢
Which hospital was he taken to?
我没问
I never asked.
中枪的人叫什么名字呢
What was the name of the man who was shot?
他们没说
They never say.
让我猜猜
And let me guess.
是你没问吧
You never asked.
保密是这里的基本原则 警探
Discretion is what this place is built on, Detective.
绅士们来这是有充分理由的
Gentlemen come here for good reason.
对自己妻子不忠
There is never a good reason
哪来什么充分理由
to be unfaithful to your wife, madam.
这话等到你结婚再说吧 孩子
Let's talk again when you're married, son.
我陷入了一个恶性循环
I'm in a vicious circle.
没有客户就意味着没有钱
No clients means no money.
没有钱就意味着没法请新员工
No money means no hiring of new staff.
我只希望等文章发表了
: I'm just hoping that when this article is published,
能吸引点新客户来
it will attract new business.
艾薇 你到底有没有在听我说话
Ivy, are you even listening to me?
抱歉
Sorry.
我刚刚读到故事中精彩的一段
I've just got to a really good bit in the story.
警探发现了另一具尸体
The detective has just found another dead body.
到处都是血
Blood everywhere.
你最近就除了埋头读书什么都不管了
AII you ever do these days is have your nose in a book.
是你让我像个正常人一样
You're the one who told me to read novels
多读点小说 而不是只读你父亲留下的法律书籍
like a normal person, instead of your father's old law books.
是我说的 但也不是除了这个别的什么都不干啊
Yes, but not all the time.
那新出炉的饼干呢
What about some freshly baked biscuits?
会有帮助吗
Will that help?
肯定有啊
Always.
摩西如何了
And what about Moses?
他会带回一两个案子吧 他什么时候回来
He brings in a case or two- - i when's he back?
不会很快吧
Not any time soon.
巴黎好像很适合他
Paris seems to suit him.
那么
Well
我们的督查呢
What about the inspector?
-我不能去找他  -为什么
I can't ask him. Why?
阿拉贝拉之后事情变得不一样了
Things aren't quite the same since Arabella.
但我以为那事已经结束了
But I thought that ended.
是 但我们很久没见过彼此了
Well, yes, but we haven't seen each other in a while.
为什么不见呢
Why not?
因为我很忙啊
Because I've been busy.
不 你不忙
No, you haven't.
去看他吧 丽兹
Go and see him, Lizzie.
别拿了
Ah! Back!
剩下的要给巴纳巴斯
The rest are for Barnabus.
借过一下
Excuse me.
吉姆
Jim.
嘿 小心点先生
Hey. Watch out, sir.
好了 非常感谢
Here we go- - thank you very much.
威廉 你来了
William, there you are.
我还以为你已经下班了
I thought perhaps you'd left for the evening.
你看上去很累
You look tired.
谢谢
: Thank you.
什么风把你给吹来了
So, to what do I owe this unexpected visit?
我就是正好经过 所以想着过来
Well, I was just passing and thought I'd pop in
看看我的老朋友
to visit my oldest friend.
经过
Passing?
-这么晚了你要去哪  -晚餐啊
To where at this time of night? Dinner.
-跟谁  -你反正也不认识
With whom? Well, you wouldn't know them.
因为根本就不存在吗
Because they don't exist?
这话什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我了解你 伊莱沙
I know you, Eliza.
你从不会经过 碰巧什么的
You neither pass nor pop,
你做事都是有预谋的
you premeditate.
不过你现在来的恐怕不是时候
Now, I'm afraid, is not a good time.
我们现在的案件数量激增
We are experiencing an unprecedented level of cases.
我没法告诉你为什么
I cannot go into why...
因为苏格兰场管辖范围
Well, because of the further expansion
的进一步扩大吧
of Scotland Yard's jurisdiction.
这在目前还是保密信息
That's classified information at the moment.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我从你桌上的报告
I read it in the report
读到的
that's on your desk.
看来你现在需要人手啊
Well, it seems you could do with more manpower.
所以我这时候来拜访真是巧了
: So, how fortuitous that I should drop by.
既然现在我纳什父子由我负责了
Since I'm now in charge at Nash and Sons,
我手下有不少人
I have a large team of men at my disposal.
我知道了
Ah, there it is.
这才是你来这的真正原因
: The real reason that you're here.
是你自己说人手不够的
You were the one who brought up being understaffed.
我只是说
All I'm saying...
是 伊莱沙 我知道你什么意思
Yes, Eliza, I know exactly what you're saying.
我一向知道你想说什么
I always know exactly what you're saying,
尽管有时你没说出口
even when you're not saying it.
晚安了
Good night.
谢谢
Thank you.
我可以确认今天他是唯一一个
I can confirm he is the only patient
被送来腿上中枪的病患
that was brought in today with a gunshot wound to the leg.
我需要知道他的名字
I need the gentleman's name.
他入院时拒绝告诉我们名字
He refused to share it when he was admitted.
之后我们还给了他鸦片酊
And since then, he's been administered laudanum
来止痛
for the pain.
所以他怕是有段时间都不能开口说话
It'll be some time before he's able to talk.
谢谢你 护士
Thank you, Nurse.
护士长
Matron.
-把帽子戴正  -是 护士长
Oh, straighten that cap, Sister! Yes, Matron.
然后去照看5号病房的患者
And see to the patient in room five!
让我想起了我太太
Reminds me of my missus.
看来今晚我们也没什么能做的了
There's not much more we can do here tonight.
我们明早再来
We'll come back in the morning
等他头脑清醒了就可以告诉我们他是谁了
when he's compos mentis, find out who he is then.
我知道他是谁
: I know exactly who he is.
我在他跟我父亲开会时见过他
I've seen him at meetings with my father.
他是个政府部长 查理
He's a government minister, Charlie.
所有的档案都在这了 督查
I have all the files here, Inspector.
等我们看完这些
And once we've gone through these,
我会带你去隔壁屋
I'll take you through to the adjoining room
那里还有更多的尸体可以看
where there are even more cadavers for your attention.
我都等不及了
I can hardly wait.
我说我们出于紧要关头时 这话可一点都没夸大其词
I do not exaggerate when I say we are bursting at the seams.
我们的验尸官 沃姆斯利先生都开始焦虑了
Our coroner, Mr. Wormsley's, agitated indeed.
他是个严谨的人
He is a precise man who, who prides himself
以一丝不苟著称
on his meticulous examinations.
但是自从这次扩张 他已经
Yet since this expansion, he has felt- -
我希望自己这么说不是种背叛
and I hope I betray no confidence here- -
他已经非常不满了
disgruntled, to say the least.
是 我理解沃姆斯利的担心 波茨先生
Yes, well, I share Mr. Wormsley's concern, Mr. Potts.
谢谢
Mm. Thank you.
威灵顿
COMMISSIONER FITZROY: Wellington.
长官
Sir.
菲茨罗伊局长
Commissioner Fitzroy.
您能亲自到这里来
May I say what a, what a pleasure it is
真是让我们蓬荜生辉啊
to have you here in person,
让我们单独谈谈
Leave us
我有件棘手的事要跟你聊聊
: I have a delicate matter to discuss with you.
梅菲尔的妓院
The brothel, in Mayfair.
中枪的男子来自内政部
The man who was shot comes from the Home Office,
而且他不是那里唯一一个有地位的绅士
and he was not the only gentleman of influence there.
大多数被盗的财产上
Most of the possessions that were stolen
都刻着个人信息
have personal messages and family crests
和家族徽章
engraved on them,
所以如果公众知道东西是在哪里丢失的
so you can imagine it would not be ideal
后果将不堪设想
if it became public knowledge where they were lost.
可以想见的到 长官
Yes, I can see that, sir.
这就是为什么我们将把查明是谁干的并取回这些财产
Which is why we are going to make it our absolute priority
作为我们的绝对优先事项
to find out who did this and to get those possessions back.
-是  -我希望你自己能亲自接手这个案子
Yes. And I want you to lead the case yourself.
长官 你之前说让我兼顾
Well, sir, you, uh, told me to specifically oversee
所有正在进行的调查
all active investigations.
我之前说的你就当没听见吧
Oh, forget what I told you.
很多人都会影响到我的预算
Many of these men have a say in my budgets.
他们会让我活得
They could make my life...
很难
...difficult.
所以你要亲自调查这个案子
So, you will lead this case
迅速并且低调的破案
and you will resolve it with speed and discretion.
如果你做不到
And, if you do not, I will hold you
就必须负全责
directly responsible.
听懂了吗 威灵顿
Is that understood, Wellington?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
我不会再说第二遍 我不会配合调查的
I won't tell you again, I want no part in this.
跟那个地方扯上任何关系对我来说都是灾难性的
Any association with that place would be catastrophic for me.
我不只是个政府部长
I'm not just a government minister,
我还是个有孩子的已婚男人
I'm a married man with children.
是
Yes.
然而 先生
Nevertheless, sir,
我还是有些问题要问你
there are some questions that I have to ask.
这么说 那个枪手闯进卧室
So, the gunman came into the bedroom,
要你把东西都给他
demanded your possessions...
我需要止痛片
: I need some pain relief!
等你回答了我的问题
And I will send for the nurse
我就叫护士进来
when you have answered my questions.
我被捕了吗
Am I under arrest?
-没有  -那你听好我的口供
No. Then here is my statement.
我在打猎时发生了意外中枪
I received this gunshot in a hunting accident.
我跟我妻子就是这么说的
This is what I have told my wife
我跟所有询问的人都会这么说
and this is what I will tell anyone who asks.
我希望这可以回答你所有的疑问 督查
I do hope that answers any further questions, Inspector.
警方新闻画报
VENDOR: "Illustrated Police News. "
"Illustrated Police News. "
刚出版的
Fresh off the press!
-警方新闻  -您好
"Illustrated Police..."Excuse me.
-给你  -谢谢
There you go. Thank you
警方新闻画报
VENDOR: "Illustrated Police News. "
早上好 克拉伦斯
Morning, Clarence.
我认为今天就是
I have decided today is the day
我们命运改变的一天
our fortunes change.
别费劲了 斯嘉丽小姐
Do not bother, Miss Scarlet.
我已经看过了 根本没有
I've already checked and there is no article.
但戈弗雷先生说了
But Mr. Godfrey specifically said
就是今天发表啊
it would be in today's edition.
记者连天上的月亮和星星都敢承诺
: Oh, well, journalists will promise the moon and stars
可一旦有更好卖的故事就不是这么回事了
until a bigger and better story comes along.
如果 我之前就建议过
If, as I had advised,
你能继续在他们那里赞助广告费的话
you had kept our advertising account with them,
他们肯定会以我们为先
they would have prioritized us,
纳什先生在这时就是这么做的
as they did when Mr. Nash was here.
可正相反 你取消了广告费用
Instead, you saw fit to cancel said account
然后把钱花在了其它地方
and spend the money elsewhere.
比如 演员 们
For instance, on actors.
我很好奇 克拉伦斯
I'm curious, Clarence.
如果你这么不满我的行事作风
If you're so dissatisfied with how I run things,
你为什么不跟其他人一样离开呢
why do you not leave like the rest?
因为
Because.
我不是个半途而废的人 斯嘉丽小姐
I am not a quitter, Miss Scarlet.
我想为此你应该更加感激才对
And I believe you could be a little more grateful for that.
我明白警方调查
I understand that a police investigation
可能对你们的生意不太好
might not be good for business.
这话有点避重就轻了
Well, that's an understatement.
警察在场的情况下
None of my clients will come within a mile
我的客人都不会在这方圆一英里以内出现
while there's a police presence.
而且这地方要是再关久一点
And I can't afford to have this place
我就承担不起了
shut down for much longer.
那就帮我好好回答问题
Then help me with my inquiries.
你不想抓到那个家伙吗
Don't you want to catch whoever did this?
他会被抓住的
Oh, he'll be caught, all right.
来我这的人可不只是那些有头有脸的大人物
It's not just the great and the good that come here.
我的客人来自各行各业
I have clients from all walks of life.
他们会替我抓住那个跛子的
They'll catch that toe- rag for me,
等他们抓到了
and when they do,
他会后悔出生在这世上的
he'll wish he'd never been born.
我需要提醒你一点 女士
I must insist that you don't take the law
你们不能私下执法 我们会抓到罪犯的
into your own hands, madam- - we will find whoever did this.
我私下参与过很多对话 督查
I'm privy to many conversations, Inspector.
法官 政客
Judges, politicians.
他们只要酒杯里倒满了威士忌 身边有女人
And when they've had their fill of whiskey and women,
就打开了话匣子
they like a nice little chat,
而我是个很好的倾听者
and I'm a very good listener.
我听说他们对伟大的苏格兰场表示不满
Word is they're not very happy with the great Scotland Yard.
从我听到的消息来看
From what I gather,
那里简直是一片狼藉
it's a shambles over there.
所以抱歉 我可没你这么自信
So, forgive me if I don't share your confidence.
长官 我收集了过去三年中
FITZROY: Sir, I've gathered files on all those with previous conviction
所有被判持械抢劫罪的犯人档案
for armed robbery for the past three years,
但有超过2000多人
but there's over 2, 000 of them.
那就抓紧咯
Better get on with it, then.
但是长官 这任务太繁重了
But, sir, it's just such a huge task
我们没有足够的人力
and we just don't have the manpower...
那就告诉你父亲我们现在的情况
: Then tell your father what a mess we're in,
因为他根本不肯听我说
because he sure as hell won't listen to me!
我刚才说的话有点过了
That was, uh, that was uncalled for.
抱歉
I apologize.
我能说句话吗 长官
Permission to speak, sir?
奥利弗 想说就说不用请求允许
Oliver, you don't have to ask permission,
你都好几天没回家了
It's just you haven't been home for days.
你 你需要休息一下
You, you need to rest.
睡觉现在对我来说太过奢侈
Sleep is a luxury that I don't have at the moment.
我们现在需要人手来查看所有的档案
Right now, we need to find a way to go through those files
然后将它们与抢手的描述对比一下
and compare them to the description of the gunman.
我们需要更多的人才行
Well, we're gonna need more men.
威廉 很高兴见到你
William, how nice to see you.
我收到你的电报了
I received your telegram.
不过我不确定
Although I must admit I was unsure
自己是否有时间安排你的事
whether I'd have time to fit you in.
你也看到了 我们目前真是超级忙
As you can see, things are extremely busy at present.
抱歉打扰一下 斯嘉丽小姐
Sorry to disturb you, Miss Scarlet,
但我需要你在惠特洛克调查上签字
but I need your sign- off on the Whitlock investigation.
过来吧
Shall we?
那么 梅菲尔的妓院
So, this brothel in Mayfair
我能告诉你的就是 这是一起持枪抢劫案
AlI I can tell you is that it was an armed robbery
其中的一名嫖客受了枪伤
where one of the punters was injured with a gunshot wound.
所以你对他的身份保密意味着
So, I assume the fact that you're keeping his identity
他是一个有影响力的人
confidential means that he's a man of influence.
伊莱沙 请不要做任何推测
Eliza, please don't assume anything.
不会有什么好结果的
It never ends well.
不过你让我的手下
Well, it's an awful lot of files
翻阅的档案实在是太多了
you wish my men to go through.
更不用说对枪手的描述有多模糊了
Not to mention how vague the description of the gunman is.
也许你愿意多出点费用
Perhaps you might be willing to negotiate a higher fee?
你到底想不想接这活儿
Do you want the job or not?
接
Yes.
-这个案子我接了  -好
I'll take the case. Good.
那今天下午把档案整理好给我
Then I'll have the files delivered this afternoon.
不要四处又嗅又刨的 伊莱沙
And no sniffing around, Eliza, or digging.
我又不是狗 威廉
I'm not a dog, William.
你不是 但你总喜欢刨根问底
No, but you are relentless.
我让你做什么你就做什么 别多做
Do only what I ask of you, nothing more.
我说到做到
My word is my bond.
最好是真的
If only that were true.
太好了
: Yes!
我真不该做这苦力
I should not be doing this donkey work.
希望你没忘 斯嘉丽小姐
Lest we forget, Miss Scarlet,
我可是个有资质的会计
I am a fully qualified accountant.
我怎么能忘呢 克拉伦斯 你这么经常的提醒我
How could I forget, Clarence, when you remind me so often?
这话就咱们两人说哈
And with just the two of us,
这活儿得花上几天时间才能完成
this task will take days to complete.
你说的对 也许我们需要找人帮忙
You're right, perhaps we do need to get some help.
我们可没钱请多余的帮手回来
: We do not have the money to pay for extra help.
谁说要付钱了
Who said anything about paying?
我收到你的消息时简直不敢相信 丽兹
I couldn't believe it when I got your note, Lizzie.
居然让我来协助真正的调查
Me, helping with a real investigation!
就像我看的小说一样
It's just like in my novel.
侦探请求他的叔叔来帮忙
The detective asks his uncle for assistance.
当然 他叔叔之前也是警察 但也还是很像啊
Yes, he's an ex- policeman, but still.
好吧
Right.
这一小部分已经完事了 我去再拿点
This little lot is done I'll go and get some more.
我们真的混到这个份儿上了 以至于你要请自己的女佣
Are we brought so low that we have to turn to your maid
来帮忙
for assistance?
她比你高效多了
She's more efficient than you.
你看完一份档案 她都看完五份了
For every one file you've checked, she's done five.
纳什先生
: Mr. Nash...
我不在乎他做什么或者不做什么
I don't care what he did or didn't do.
现在这里我说了算
I'm in charge now.
既然你这么迷恋纳什先生
And if you're so enamored with Mr. Nash,
你为什么不跟他去巴黎呢
why didn't you go to Paris with him?
干嘛
What?
态度好点不行吗
Go easy, hey?
我不需要你给我管理员工们的建议
I don't need advice on how to manage my employees.
你就一个员工
Employee, singular.
你还是个孩子的时候
When you were a girl
拜托了 天
Oh, please, God, no.
好吧 我去跟他聊聊
: Fine, I'll talk to him.
因为我一心让咱们这事务所维持下去
In my determination to keep this agency afloat,
所以有时候说话可能过于简练了
I may come across as a little terse sometimes.
为此我道歉
I apologize.
我刚才想说的是 纳什先生
AIIIwas going to say about Mr. Nash
养了一大批有偿线人
is that he has an army of paid informants,
其中包括
including girls who work
在伦敦不同妓院工作的女孩
at many different brothels across London.
我到哪能找到这些线人的信息
Where would Ifind information on these informants?
之前为什么没人告诉过我这里有个保险柜
Why wasn't I told this was in here?
纳什先生希望能确保
Well, Mr. Nash likes to keep the identity
他的线人身份保密
of his informants confidential.
可我是首席调查员啊
I'm the chief investigator!
你是唯一一个调查员
You're the only investigator.
好了
Right, um.
警方线人
Police informants.
法律界线人
Legal informants.
政府线人
Government informants.
在这里
Here we are.
夜晚的女士们
Ladies of the night.
我喜欢纳什先生
I adore Mr. Nash.
对我总是很好
Always so good to me.
一个好人 大家都喜欢他
A very fair man- - everyone loves him.
不如我们聊点与纳什先生无关的
Perhaps we could talk about something other than Mr. Nash.
你是在极乐境上班对吧
So, you work at the Temple of Elysium.
不可饶恕啊
For my sins.
我听说过那里
I've heard of it.
我觉得这想法很聪明
I always thought it very clever.
一个以神话天堂为主题的妓院
A brothel themed as a mythological paradise.
听过来的警察说
Hm, well, according to the copper that came by,
女人都去不了极乐世界呢
women weren't even allowed in Elysium.
他说的对
Well, he's right.
它是希腊神话中的
It was one of the three realms of the underworld
冥府三界之一
in Greek mythology.
地狱（塔尔塔罗斯）水仙平原
Tartarus, the Asphodel Meadows,
然后就是极乐境 神青睐的
and then there was Elysium, an Eden for heroes
英雄们的所在地
favored by the gods.
我可以告诉你 亲爱的
Well, I can tell you, darling,
来找我的男人们可不是什么英雄
the men that visit me ain't no heroes.
那么这场枪击
So, this shooting.
那个枪手的描述
The description of the gunman- -
中等身高 金发蓝色眼睛
average height, fair hair, blue eyes- -
有点太泛泛了
it's a little generic.
而且都是假的
It's a pack of lies, too.
他很高 褐色头发褐色眼睛
He was tall, brown hair, brown eyes.
她让我和其他姑娘
Me and the other girls were told to lie
对警察撒谎的
to the coppers by her.
赫拉夫人
Madam Hera.
当然这不是她真名
That's not her real name, of course,
就跟雅典娜也不是我的真名一样
just like Athena ain't mine.
她为什么让你们撒谎呢
Why would she tell you to lie?
听说她找人帮忙自己去寻枪手了
Word is, she called in a favor to find the gunman herself.
你敢惹夫人那就是自寻死路
You cross the madam at your own peril.
可怜的老迪米特里就验证了这一点
Poor old Dimitrie found that out.
迪米特里
Dimitrie?
抢劫发生时
The watchman that was on
值班的门卫
when the robbery took place.
她解雇了那个可怜的家伙
She sacked the poor sod.
欢迎来到所罗门
Welcome to Solomon's.
请问有什么事
How can I help?
所罗门在吗
Is Solomon here?
我叔叔回牙买加走亲戚去了
I'm afraid my uncle's gone back to Jamaica to visit family.
也许你可以帮我
Well, perhaps you could help me.
我是他的熟人 斯嘉丽小姐
I'm an acquaintance of his, Miss Scarlet.
我在找一个人 一个门卫
I'm looking for man, a watchman.
他刚刚被人从梅菲尔妓院解雇
He was dismissed from a, a brothel in Mayfair.
我需要找到他的地址 我想跟他谈谈
I need to find his address- - I wish to speak with him.
我不知道你在说什么
I'm afraid I have no idea what you're talking about.
这是买东西的地方 斯嘉丽小姐
This is a shop to buy things in, Miss Scarlet.
说到这个
And speaking of which,
我们今早到了批新货
we've just had a new delivery this very morning.
来自喜马拉雅山脉的金面蝴蝶
The golden vamp butterfly from the Himalayan mountains.
非常稀有
Very rare.
北半球没有
There are no golden vamp butterflies
金面蝴蝶
in the Northern Hemisphere.
我搞错了 对
Ah, my mistake, yeah.
这是来自马达加斯加的金面蝴蝶
This is the golden vamp from Madagascar.
而且这种蝴蝶也不是纯金色的
And nor are they completely golden,
只是翅膀尖带有金色
just the tips of their wings.
很漂亮
This is very pretty.
如果我买一个呢
What if I bought one?
那我帮你包起来
I'll wrap it up for you.
如果我买两个呢
What if I bought two?
那我就都帮你包起来
Then I'll wrap them both.
三个呢
How about three?
你说的是一个门卫吗
A watchman, you say?
我去拿笔
Let me get my pen.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
辛克莱先生
Mr. Sinclaire.
你好吗 斯嘉丽小姐
How are you, Miss Scarlet?
忙
Busy.
总是很忙呢
Always such a busy, busy bee.
应该是自打你接手了
I suppose, since you've taken over
纳什父子之后吧 虽然他也没有儿子
at Nash and Sons, not that he has any sons,
时间宝贵
time is precious.
你想要什么 辛克莱先生
What do you want, Mr. Sinclaire?
就是想告诉你我有多受伤
Why, just to tell you how hurt I am.
当我听说你去找我的下属戈弗雷先生
When I learned that you'd gone to my underling, Mr. Godfrey,
而不是直接来找我
instead of directly to me,
刊物的首席记者时
the chief correspondent of our esteemed publication,
简直像是在我的心上戳了一刀
it was like a dagger to my heart.
你还有心呢 辛克莱先生
You have a heart, Mr. Sinclaire.
这可真是个好消息
That is welcome news.
我对自己说 巴兹尔
”Basil, "I said to myself,
你和斯嘉丽小姐不是老熟人吗
"You and Miss Scarlet are old acquaintances, are you not?
为什么她会这么做呢
Why on Earth would she do such a thing? "
上次我们合作时
The last time we worked together,
你发表了一堆谎言 还记得吗
you printed a pack of lies- - does that help?
谎言
Ooh, lies, you say?
是指你给年轻的戈弗雷先生看到的那些吗
Like the ones you fed young Mr. Godfrey?
看起来 因为迫切地想要宣扬你的成功
It seems that in your eagerness to laud your success,
你做出了不诚实的举动 道德滑坡了
it has led you down the slippery slope of dishonesty.
天呐 天呐
Oh, dear, dear me.
你知道吗 我恰好得知
You see, I happen to know for a fact
纳什先生的所有员工都背弃了你
that Mr. Nash's entire staff have deserted you,
他的客户们也是
and so, too, his book of clients.
所以 作为首席记者
And so, in my capacity as chief correspondent,
我决定这篇文章将由我执笔
I have decided that I will be the one to write the article,
以真相为基础
and it shall be one based on the truth:
伦敦昔日最成功的
that the once most successful
私家侦探事务所
private investigation agency in London
如今已处于破产边缘
is now on the verge of collapse.
而这一切都要归功于
And it is all thanks
你这位女私家侦探
to the lady detective.
日安 斯嘉丽小姐
Good day, Miss Scarlet.
出发
Ride on!
好的先生 驾
Sir- hup!
-让他走吧  -好的长官
Let him go. Sir.
怎么样
PHELPS: Any luck?
他有不在场证明 和其他人一样
He's got an alibi, just like all the others.
那再抓一些回来
So, we round up some more?
你还是有希望成为一名好警探的 查理
We'll make a detective of you yet, Charlie.
威廉
William.
威灵顿督察
Inspector Wellington.
威灵顿督察 菲尔普斯警探
Inspector Wellington, Detective Phelps.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
准备马车
Get the wagons ready.
去门外等我
I'll meet you out front.
我有点事要告诉你 威廉
I have something I need to tell you, William,
你能保证不动怒吗
but will you promise to remain calm?
你雇了演员来假装成你手下的侦探
You hired actors to pose as your staff of detectives?
我就知道你会有这种反应
I knew you'd react like this.
你通过撒谎让我聘请了你 你还想让我怎么反应
You fooled me into hiring you! How would you like me to react?
至少我还算体面 来亲自告诉你了
Well, at least I did the decent thing to tell you myself,
没有让你从辛克莱的小报上读到
rather than you reading it in Sinclaire's rag,
你要是体面 一开始就不应该骗我
The decent thing was not to lie to me in the first place.
你想说的话 我都和我自己
There's nothing you can say that I haven't already said
-说过了  -我可不这么认为
to myself. Oh, I'm quite sure that there is.
你的工作这么舒服
It's all very well
没什么可担心的
for you in your comfortable job.
而我已经好几周没睡觉了 天天为我的工作发愁
I haven't slept for weeks worrying about mine.
老天 伊莱沙 我的工作和舒服一点也不沾边
My God, Eliza, there is nothing comfortable about my job,
如果你不是只关注自己
and if you had any shred of concern
能关心关心别人
for anyone other than yourself,
你不会不知道的
then you would know this!
你好 斯嘉丽小姐
FITZROY: Good day, Miss Scarlet.
你还好吗
Is, is all well?
一点也不好
Not remotely.
但没关系了
But never mind that.
妓院抢劫案是你负责吗
You're on the brothel robbery?
是的
I am.
好
Good.
我有些信息想和你分享
Because I have some information I'd like to share with you.
所以 鸨母编造了枪手的模样
So, the madam lied about the description of the gunman.
显然是的
Apparently so.
我还派了人去找被开掉的门卫
I've also put the feelers out to find this dismissed watchman.
谢谢你 这些信息非常有用
Thank you, this is most helpful.
奥利弗
Oliver.
威灵顿督察
Inspector Wellington,
你觉得他最近状态怎么样
how have you found him recently?
不瞒你说 我挺担心他的
I cannot lie, um, I'm concerned about him.
他已经好几天没回家了
He hasn't been home for days.
他把所有精力都放在了这起抢劫案上
He's putting all his attention on this robbery,
疏忽了其他案件
to the detriment of other cases,
案子都堆成山了
of which there are many.
那么 让我来帮帮你吧
Well, then, let me help you.
把你们的调查结果告诉我
Share your findings with me.
但这次调查是严格保密的
Uh, this is a highly confidential investigation.
恐怕我不能告诉你
I'm afraid I cannot.
不过
However,
如果我把档案留在桌上
if I were to leave the file here,
出去一小会儿
and if I were to just pop out for a moment,
如果有人在我不知情的情况下看了档案
then if someone were to read the file without my knowledge,
那
well
被射伤的男人
The man who was shot.
知道是谁了吗
Any identity yet?
第四页
: Page four.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
你怎么没穿制服
Why are you not in your uniform?
我不明白
I don't understand.
你是今天新入职的詹姆斯护士吧
You are Nurse James, due to start today?
这房间乱得可怕
Well, this room is a disgrace!
这些脏衣服昨天就应该处理掉了
These soiled clothes should have been disposed of yesterday!
处理好后 给他整理床铺
And when you have done that, his bed needs remaking,
记录体温 更换绷带
his temperature recorded, and bandage changed.
把这些衣服拿到地下室去
So get these clothes down to the basement
烧掉
ready to be incinerated,
换上制服 马上来找我报到
get into your uniform, and report back immediately!
-听清楚了吗  -能让我说了吗
Is that clear? If you would just let me speak.
我不是护士
I'm not a nurse
我叫伊莱沙·斯嘉丽
My name is Eliza Scarlet.
是一名私家侦探 还有拜托
I'm a private detective- and, please,
拜托千万别说 你是个啥
don't say, "You're a what? "
走走
OFFICER: Come on, come on!
快走 别浪费时间
Come on, we haven't got all day.
快快快
Go, go, go!
把这些人带进去 查理
WILLIAM: Get this lot inside, Charlie.
好嘞 丑八怪 赶紧的
PHELPS: AII right, you ugly lot, hurry up!
不然就把你们的蛋踢爆
: Or you'll feel my boot where the sun don't shine!
你在这里啊 长官
There you are, sir.
极乐境的案子有新信息
I have new information on the Elysium case.
妓院鸨母说谎了
The madam of the brothel lied.
枪手不是金发蓝眼睛 中等身高
The gunman wasn't fair, blue eyes, or medium height.
正相反 他是高个子 褐色头发 褐色眼睛
He was the opposite: tall, brown hair, brown eyes.
谁说的
According to whom?
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
她看上去很确定
She seemed quite certain of it, too.
我得去找赫拉夫人一趟了
I think I'll pay Madam Hera a little visit.
艾薇呢
Where's Ivy?
去给一个叫巴纳巴斯的人做晚饭了
Gone to make dinner for someone called Barnabus.
但她带了一箱
She did take a box of files with her
档案去查 这个是给你的
to work through- - oh, this came for you.
拖欠房租的法院传票
It's a court summons for rent arrears.
就没有什么好消息吗 克拉伦斯
I really could do with some good news, Clarence.
你在找的那个门卫
Well, the watchman you've been looking for.
他在你的办公室里
He's in your office.
所以 抢劫发生后 鸨母解雇了你
So, the madam dismissed you after the robbery.
因为我跑到外面去呼救了 没有抓住枪手
Because I ran outside for help instead of tackling the gunman.
20年前我来到这里 想要过上更好的生活
I came here 20 years ago in search for better life.
但是做门卫的这些年来
But, as a watchman, I have spent those years
得到的却是拳打脚踢和枪伤
getting beaten up and shot at.
年轻的时候我不在乎 但是
And when I was young, I did not mind, but...
我年纪大了
I'm getting old.
我还有孩子 我想看他们长大
I have children I want to see grow up.
而那女的害得我
And because of that woman,
今天晚上没办法让家人
I will not be able to put some food
吃上饭了
on my family's table tonight.
我不用忠诚于她
I have no loyalty to her,
所以我想告诉你一些事情
so I will tell you something.
你说
I'm listening.
她让我对警察撒谎
She told me to lie to the police.
我呼救的时候 没有看到有枪手离开妓院
When I was calling for help, I saw no gunman leave the brothel.
如果你没有看到枪手离开 他又是怎么逃离的呢
But if you didn't see the gunman leave, then how did he get away?
有后门吗
A back entrance?
妓院没有后门
There is no back entrance.
我不能上楼
I was forbidden to ever go upstairs,
但是我听说
but I've heard
有个密道能进出
there is a secret way in and out.
妓院旁边的大楼
DIMITRIE: The building that adjoins the brothel
以前是高档绅士俱乐部
was once an exclusive gentlemen's club.
几年前关门了
It shut down years ago,
但那里曾是名流权贵爱去的地方
but it was once frequented by the rich and powerful,
政客 甚至还有王子
by politicians and even princes.
据说里面有一扇连接门 供客人
Legend has it that the clients would use a connecting door
秘密地进入妓院
into the brothel as a discreet way in.
如果真有这扇门
If the door exists,
我想枪手就是从那里逃走的
I believe that's how the gunman escaped.
太阳神的三个儿子
ELIZA: Three sons of Titan.
宙斯 天神
Zeus, god of the sky.
波塞冬 海神
Poseidon, god of the sea.
哈迪斯 掌管冥府三界之神
And Hades, god of the three realms of the underworld:
地狱 水仙平原
Tartarus, the Asphodel Meadows,
和极乐境
and Elysium.
弹孔
A bullet hole.
这我倒是不知道
WILLIAM: Well, that's news to me.
什么叫被归还了
What do you mean they've been returned?
就是字面意思
Exactly that.
所有被偷的财物都在这个盒子里
Everything stolen is in this box.
今天早上被放在了大门外
It was outside the entrance this morning.
我也不知道是谁放的
I've got no idea who left it.
我会把这些归还给
So, I will return these
它们本来的主人 案子就结了
to their rightful owners, and case is closed.
案子我说结才能结
The case is closed when I say it is.
我要把这盒东西
I'lI be taking the contents of that box
带回苏格兰场
back to Scotland Yard,
登记作证物
where it will be logged as evidence.
而你嘛
As for you,
你也跟我来一趟 做一份声明
you'll come with me and make a statement
解释清楚这些被偷的财物
explaining how you came to be in possession
是怎么到你手里的
of these stolen goods.
督察 我很确信你的上级
I'm quite sure, Inspector, that your superiors
让你快速低调地
have instructed you to close this case
结了这个案子
with speed and discretion.
把这些昂贵之物
Taking these valuables to Scotland Yard,
以及我 带回警局
and, indeed, me,
恐怕和低调
I would argue that is the
背道而驰吧
very opposite of discretion.
那么我们就说好了
So, we're agreed.
我把这些还给我的客人
I will return these to my clients,
你离开我的地盘
and you will leave my premises
别再来烦我了
and bother me no more.
你还忘了什么吧 夫人
See, you're forgetting something, madam.
医院里还躺着一位在你这里被射伤的先生
There is a man lying in hospital who was shot on these premises.
我知道的情况是 可怜的部长
Last I heard, the poor minister,
坚称自己是在打猎时受的伤
he was adamant that he was wounded in a hunting accident.
要是他的妻子牵扯进来的话
No more days out shooting for him.
他就再也不能出门打猎了
Not if his wife has anything to do with it.
我没兴趣也懒得再
I do not have the appetite nor the inclination
和你争辩了 伊莱沙
for another argument, Eliza.
我这一天天的已经够烦了
My day has been vexing enough.
我不是来和你吵的
I do not come to argue.
我是来告诉你
I come to tell you I've made
我发现了妓院案的新线索
a discovery on the brothel case.
不 伊莱沙
No, Eliza
我知道枪手是谁了
I know who the gunman is.
部长被射伤的卧室里
There's a hidden door
有一道密门 门后是
that leads from the bedroom where the minister was shot
一座废弃大楼里的房间
into a room of an abandoned building,
我在那里找到了一颗子弹
and it's there that I found a bullet.
我想是枪手逃跑时走火了
I believe it was discharged by the gunman as he escaped.
这是部长的裤子
Trousers belonging to the minister.
本来要被医护人员火化了
They were due to be incinerated at the hospital.
这和子弹有什么关系
So, what does this have to do with the bullet?
子弹上沾了这个东西
This was attached to the bullet.
我认得这布料的图案
I recognized the pattern on the cloth.
我想起来我在医院见过
I knew I'd seen it before at hospital.
那为什么 为什么部长要撒谎
So, why, why would the minister lie
说枪手在卧室里射伤了他
and say that the gunman shot him in the bedroom?
因为他就是枪手 威廉
Because he is the gunman, William.
我有什么必要抢劫啊
Why on Earth would I want to stage a robbery?
我怎么说也是个政府部长
I'm a government minister, for heaven's sake!
我查了一下你的情况 先生
Well, I've done some digging on you, sir,
看起来 你也有着不小的财务麻烦
and it would appear that you're also in grave financial straits.
要我说 这个动机就足够了
I would say that that is motive enough.
你是个初级部长 要想升官
Being a junior minister must be a costly business
肯定得花不少钱
if you hope for a promotion.
晚餐 看戏 举办派对 用好酒招待
Dinners, theater trips, hosting parties with the right wine.
肯定会造成财务压力
It must be a strain on one's resources.
那些人说什么 重要的不是认识人
Anyone who tells you, "It's not who you know,
而是你的学识 都是骗人的
but what you know, "is a liar.
我需要钱来升官
I needed the money to rise up the ranks,
来讨好那些能让我平步青云的人
to impress those with the power to help me advance.
所以你就在没有人会承认去过的地方
So, you staged a robbery in a place where no one
策划了一起抢劫案
would want to admit to being.
这是内政部的人最喜欢去的妓院
It is the favored brothel by those at the Home Office.
应该是实施抢劫的绝佳场所
It seemed like the perfect place to do it.
所以 当大家都以为你喝得醉醺醺地躺在床上时
So, while everyone thought you were in bed intoxicated,
你乔装成了枪手
you disguised yourself as the gunman.
轮到抢劫自己的时候
And when it came to robbing yourself,
你将房间伪造成打斗过的样子
you staged a fight to make it look like
好像你激烈反抗过
there'd been a struggle.
我本来打算把枪手的衣物
I planned to leave the gunman's attire
和偷来的东西放在隔壁房间
and what Id stolen in the room next door.
然后回到床上 还是那个喝醉的部长
I would then get back into bed as the drunk minister,
没有人会发现的
and no one would be any the wiser.
然而 我听见值班门卫在外面呼救
But then I heard the watchman on duty yelling for help outside,
我就
and I
我就慌了
I flew into a panic.
我钻过密门 去到了废弃的房间
As I squeezed through the door to the disused room,
结果绊了一跤摔倒了
Istumbled and fell.
手枪走火了
And the handgun went off.
我这是第一次用手枪
I've never used a handgun before.
从白教堂小酒馆的一个粗人手上买来的
Bought it from some rough type in a pub in Whitechapel.
而你得掩盖你把自己射伤的事实
But you had to cover the fact you'd been shot,
所以朝卧室的地板也开了一枪
so you put a bullet in the bedroom floor, too.
我把所有事情都告诉鸨母了
Itold the madam everything
我只能这么做
I had to.
我需要她的帮助
I needed her help.
她听说我在她的地盘上搞了这么一出 非常生气
She was livid Id done such a thing in her place of business,
吩咐我别说出去
so she instructed that I keep my mouth shut.
她来消除证据
And she would get rid of the evidence.
所以她才假装追寻
Which is why she pretended to track down
被偷的财物
the stolen possessions,
但实际上 这些东西一直在她手里
when, in fact, she had them all the time.
她会把财物尽数归还
They would be returned to their owners,
这个案子就能迅速低调地了结了
and the case would be closed quickly and discreetly.
德拉瓦尔部长会辞去职务
COMMISSIONER FITZROY: Minister Delaware will resign
默默离开
and go away quietly.
而这位赫拉夫人
And this Madam Hera,
-她和这一切也脱不了干系  -噢 不不
she's up to her eyes in all this, too. Oh, no, no.
别去招惹她
She's to be left alone.
她知道的事情太多 牵扯太广了
She knows too much about too many.
长官
Sir, um,
这次业务扩张压得我们喘不过气
this expansion is crippling us.
我们的人手和资源都不够
We lack the manpower and the resources to cope.
我最怕的是 我会让我的手下
My biggest fear is that I am sending my men
陷入他们尚未准备好的处境
into situations that they are ill prepared for.
这样下去 会有人受伤的
Someone is going to get hurt.
你想让我怎么办
What would you have me do?
我又不能凭空变出钱来
I cannot pluck money out of thin air.
是 长官 但是
No, sir, but, um
或许这个案子可以
But perhaps this, this case can,
可以让你在内政部的人面前有更多话语权
can give you some more sway with the Home Office.
毕竟 我们不往外声张 也是帮了他们一个大忙
After all, it's for their sake that we're staying quiet.
你是让我勒索他们啊
You are asking me to blackmail them,
勒索政府部门
a government department.
不 当然不是了 长官 不是勒索 而是
No, of course not, sir, not blackmail, more, um.
有更多谈判的筹码
More leverage to negotiate.
要是我能按我的意思来 我会让你立刻滚蛋
If I had my way, I would dismiss you with immediate effect
就因为你提出了这么个建议
for the mere suggestion of such a thing.
但考虑到目前变动太多 这么做对谁都没有好处
: But given the flux we are in, that would benefit no one.
这个案子 你把嘴闭严实了
You are to keep your mouth shut about this case.
明白了吗 威灵顿
Is that clear, Wellington?
明白 长官
Perfectly, sir.
你也只是在为你的手下着想
ELIZA: You were simply thinking of your men.
但局长不这么认为
WILLIAM: The police commissioner didn't quite see it like that.
你想让我去找他聊聊吗
Would you like me to have a word with him?
看到你笑真好
It's nice to see you smile.
最近没什么让我开心的事情
Well, I haven't had much to smile about recently.
抱歉我对你撒谎了
I'm sorry I lied to you.
我试着指挥纳什的员工
I did try to lead Nash's men.
但他们只把我当作专横的女人
But they just saw me as some bossy woman.
你不是专横 伊莱沙
You're not bossy, Eliza.
你是意志坚定
You are determined.
事情的发展和我希望的不太一样
Things haven't quite turned out how I'd hoped.
有的时候我会想
Sometimes I do wonder.
这一切值得吗
If it's all worth it?
你是个好侦探 伊莱沙 非常好
You are a good detective, Eliza, very good.
无论以后发生什么
And whatever happens from here,
你都能找到解决办法的
you'll find a way to make it work.
你总能找到的
You always do.
你这么说 是想让我
Are you just saying that so that I pay
付明晚的饭钱吗
for dinner tomorrow evening?
我不知道我们要一起吃晚饭诶
I wasn't aware that we were due to dine.
每个月的最后一个星期三 我们都会约晚饭呀
Well, the last Wednesday of every month, we dine,
刚好就是明天
and that just happens to be tomorrow.
好久没有晚上出门放松放松了
It's been a while since we enjoyed an evening out.
是的
It has.
好 别再熬通宵了
Well, no more burning the midnight oil.
你今晚一定得回家
You must go home tonight
休息 明晚吃饭时睡着
and rest- - I will not have you falling asleep
-可不行  -我收回我刚刚说的话
at the table. I take back what I said.
你确实挺专横的
You are bossy.
晚安 伊莱沙
Good night, Eliza.
晚安 威廉
Good night, William.
晚安 督察
IVY: Night, Inspector.
晚安 艾薇
WILLIAM: Night, Ivy.
我在你让我查的档案里
I've found something in these files
找到了点东西
you asked me to look through.
这案子已经结案了 艾薇
The case is closed, Ivy.
不是关于枪手的
It's not about the gunman.
是另一个毫不相干的人
It's about someone else entirely.
我现在明白 你为什么不像其他人一样
Now I understand why you haven't sought another position
换家公司了
like the others.
或者跟纳什先生去巴黎
Or gone to Paris with Mr. Nash.
原来是因为你有过
The small issue of a criminal record
犯罪记录
would have put paid to that!
档案里说 你为不止一个
You are mentioned as an associate to not one,
而是三个犯罪团伙做过会计
but three criminal gangs as their accountant.
而且做得还不怎么样 毕竟你还因为税务欺诈
And not a very successful one, given you've served time
而坐过牢
for taxation fraud.
我无处可去时 是纳什先生雇佣了我
Mr. Nash hired me when no one else would.
我会永远感激他
And I shall be forever grateful for that.
我去拿大衣和帽子吧
I shall fetch my coat and hat.
不 不用
No, don't.
我们都不是完美的 克拉伦斯
Neither of us is perfect, Clarence.
如果我答应你 我以后工作时会更随和一些
And if I promise to be more accommodating,
我也希望你能答应我 不要再拿我和纳什先生作比较了
I would like you to promise to stop comparing me to Mr. Nash.
所以我俩是一条船上的人了
So, we are stuck with each other.
看起来是这样的
It seems so.
克拉伦斯 我们要共同努力
Together, Clarence, we shall once more
让这家事务所再创辉煌
make this agency successful.
那些看不起我们的人走着瞧吧
And those that underestimate us should do so at their own peril.
对了 说起这个我们的妓院线人雅典娜
Oh, um, on that, our info mant rom the brothel, Athena,
来讨要费用了
came by for her fee.
她话可真多
She likes to chat, that one.
她和我说了点事情 你或许有兴趣
She told me something that may be of interest to you.
辛克莱先生
Mr. Sinclaire.
斯嘉丽小姐
Ah, Miss Scarlet.
这么巧呀
How serendipitous.
还想着今天下午去找你呢
I was intending to pay you a visit this very afternoon.
你倒亲自过来了
It appears you have saved me a journey.
这是我刚写的
Here is the story I have
关于你
just penned about you and your.
落千丈的可悲故事
: lamentable fall from grace.
你是想现在读呢
Would you care to read it now?
还是想出版后再读
Or perhaps you would rather wait until it's published,
我想在明天的报纸里
which I believe it will be,
你就能读到了
in tomorrow morning's edition.
不 不会的 辛克莱先生
No, it will not, Mr. Sinclaire.
实际上 你会立刻回到办公室
In fact, you will return immediately to the office
撤回这篇文章
and retract the article.
我为什么要这么做
And why on Earth would I do that?
你估计已经听说了
You've no doubt heard about the robbery that took place
梅菲尔妓院极乐境的抢劫案
at the brothel in Mayfair, the Temple of Elysium.
鸨母让女孩们
The madam has asked her girls
把失窃的财物还给她们的
to reunite their regular clients
老客户
with their stolen possessions.
其中一个女孩
And one of those girls just happens to be
我恰好认识
an associate of mine.
雅典娜
Athena?
她好心让我把这个还给你
She kindly allowed me to return this to you.
你的名字刻得真不错
Very nice inscription of your name.
但没有刻上你的首席记者职位诶
No mention of you being chief correspondent, though.
或许下一次 你的妻子
Perhaps the next time your wife
为礼物刻字的时候 会记得刻上你的职称
inscribes a gift, she'll remember to include it.
哦对了 你放心
Oh, and just to reassure you,
威灵顿督察已经把这块表登记为证物了
Inspector Wellington has logged it as evidence.
如果有必要证明
So, should the need ever arise to prove
你去过妓院的话 应该不是难事
your presence at the brothel, it will not be hard to do so.
日安 辛克莱先生
Good day, Mr. Sinclaire.
谢谢
Thank you.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
失陪了
If you will excuse me,
我要和我的好朋友喝茶
I'm taking tea with my good friend.
西奥博尔德
Theobald!
你们想雇佣我
You wish to hire me?
非常时期 非常手段
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
我相信 我一个人去看望这么一个
ELIZA: I'm sure I'll be fine to visit such a dangerous,
危险的暴力罪犯
violent criminal.
没问题的
Alone.